(Sheldon:)Once while he was trying to watch
The Incredibles.
(Sheldon:)Penny.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Sheldon:)So, Penny, I understand...
...you'd like to learn more about flags.
- I can't tell you how many times...
...I've been at a party, everyone's talking
about flags and I just couldn't join in.
(Sheldon:)Well, you came to the right place.
(Penny:)I'm sorry, can we just pause for a minute?
(Sheldon:)What's wrong?
I think it'd look more natural
if you talked to me instead of the camera.
You know, like a real conversation?
(Penny:)It's something we work on
in acting class.
(Sheldon:)Interesting.
(Sheldon:)A few people in the Comments section
have said that my delivery is robotic.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps that isn't the compliment
it sounds like.
Let's try it again. Maybe this time
you could work on body language a bit.
When you're hunched like that,
you're shutting the audience out.